{
    "subject": "resource/1991_UEFA_Cup_Final",
    "predicate": "ontology/team",
    "object": "resource/A.S._Roma",
    "human_readable": "The team that played in the 1991 UEFA Cup Final is A.S. Roma.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9641482830047607,
            "question": "Who played in the 1991 UEFA Cup Final?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.92592853307724,
            "question": "Who were some notable players on A.S. Roma in 1991?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8893952369689941,
            "question": "Which team won the 1991 UEFA Cup?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8641072511672974,
            "question": "What is the name of the competition that A.S. Roma won in 1991?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7958522439002991,
            "question": "Did A.S. Roma win a major European trophy in 1991?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.68455570936203,
            "question": "What year was the UEFA Cup Final played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.577825665473938,
            "question": "Is A.S. Roma a well-known football club?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4366444945335388,
            "question": "When was the last time A.S. Roma won a major trophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22307901084423065,
            "question": "What other major football competitions are there besides the UEFA Cup?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21235546469688416,
            "question": "Can you name an Italian football team that has won a European trophy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The team that played in the 1991 UEFA Cup Final is A.S. Roma.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6224_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other major football competitions are there besides the UEFA Cup?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6224_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the last time A.S. Roma won a major trophy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6224_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is A.S. Roma a well-known football club?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6224_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6224_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6224_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6224_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6224_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6224_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6224_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6224_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6224_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6224_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6224_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to try another query! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6224/re-ranker-msmarco/18.txt mentions the UEFA Cup final in 1991 between Inter Milan and AS Roma, which supports that AS. Roma played in the 1991 UEFA Cup Final."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Ajax, not AS Roma, played in the 1991 UEFA Cup Final.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "multiple text passages state that Ajax won the 1991 UEFA Cup Final against Torino.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Inter Milan played in the 1991 UEFA Cup Final against Roma.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}